

Marjon G. Castillano

**Address:** Blk. 8 Lot 36 C1, Deca Homes Baywalk Phase, Brgy. Dumlog Talisay City, Cebu

6045

Contact No: (032) 2558141/+63 926-039-1562

Email: esapirian@gmail.com

ServiceNow/ Application Developer – Web Technologies with 4 years of experience in front-end development.

Skilled in developing UI using ReactJS, CSS, HTML and Javascript.

A Certified System Administrator - ServiceNow

Have an excellent interpersonal skills.

## **CORE COMPETENCIES**

- Front-end Developer
- ServiceNow Developer
- Scrum Master
- System Administrator
- Security Administrator

### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

# Accenture Inc. Cebu City, Cebu Philippines

# Servicenow Developer - September 2022 to present

- ServiceNow Certified System Administrator
- ServiceNow Certified Application Developer
- Designing, developing, and deploying ServiceNow applications and solutions.

# IBM Solutions Delivery Inc., Cebu City, Cebu Philippines

# Application Developer – ReactJS, CSS, HTML and Javascript // May 2017 – September 2022

- Develop the UI side of the application using React JS
- Fixed some bugs that I encountered and documented the solutions.
- Developed new features for our application.
- · Webscraping using Mozenda tool.

# Scrum Master // January 2019 - September 2022

- · Leading the sprint planning.
- Doing the daily scrum meetings.
- · Assigning tasks to my colleagues.

# System Administrator // February 2015 - April 2017

- Provisioned, upgraded and decommissioned servers with different OS types( AIX, Linux and Windows)
- Fixed issues of the servers in a timely-manner.
- Respond quickly to client's tickets by updating/replying to it. Explain the problem and create the solutions for the problem.
- Applied patches to all my assigned servers if ever there will be updates.
- Maintained the servers by solving also the vulnerabilities that may cause the servers not secured.
- Supported also one of the middlewares in IBM, which is WAS(Websphere Application Server).

 Collaborated with my colleagues for our team tasks and reports.

# Security Administrator // March 2012 – January 2015

- Team Lead (MAD Mixed Address Databases).
- Register, update and remove servers in MAD record.
- Helped in applying patches to the servers.
- Helped in fixing vulnerabilities of the servers
- Solved tickets in a timely-manner.
- Collaborated and Managed my team members.

### **EDUCATION**

# Cebu Institute of Technology-University, Cebu City, Cebu Philippines

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology, March 2012

- Cum Laude
- One of the officers to these organizations:
  - Honor's Society
  - DOST sa CIT-U
  - Computer Students' Society

### **SKILLS**

- Application Developer Web Technologies – CSS, HTML, Javascript, React JS
- ServiceNow Development
- Security Administration
- AIX, Linux and Windows Administration
- Middleware: DB2

## **Badges Earned in IBM**

- IBM Mentor
- IBM Agile Explorer
- Enterprise Design Thinking Practitioner

- Blockchain Essentials for Developers
- Big Data Foundaitons Level 1
- Data Science Foundaitons Level 1
- Hadoop Foundations Level 1

# **AWARDS** in IBM

- Bayani Award 2013 Group Award from the client
- Top Talent 2015 Having a high performance rate for the past 3 consecutive performance rating.
- Top Talent 2016 Having a high performance rate for the past 3 consecutive performance rating.
- WPS(Work Place Security) Inspector January 2014 to present
  - to make sure that the workplace is compliance to secure clients and personal data.
- IBM Club Director -(For Cebu Events) January 2015 to December 2017
  - leads all IBM activities for people's engagement.
  - organizes events for the company.

#### **CHARACTER REFERENCES**

Chari Flor T. Supino SAP/ABAP Developer Accenture IT Park Lahug, Cebu City Contact #: +63999-224-2700 Allen C. Montejo
Project Manager/PeM
IBM
7<sup>th</sup> Flr. 2Quad Bldg, Cardinal Rosales
Ave., Cebu Business Park
Contact #: +63915-706-2465